<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Tag: English | EverET.org]]></title>
  <link href="http://everet.org/tag/english/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://everet.org/"/>
  <updated>2013-01-15T00:25:15+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://everet.org/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Stupid ET]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[改变你一生的5句英文励志铭言]]></title>
    <link href="http://everet.org/2012/01/inspiration.html"/>
    <updated>2012-01-23T21:52:29+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://everet.org/2012/01/inspiration</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h4 id="always-be-a-first-rate-version-of-yourself-instead-of-a-second-rate-version-of-somebody-else---judy-garland">1.Always be a first-rate version of yourself, instead of a second-rate version of somebody else. - Judy Garland</h4>

<h4 id="judy-garland3050">永远做自己的一流版本，永不做他人的二流版本。——朱迪·嘉兰（Judy Garland，美国30~50年代著名影星）</h4>

<p>I believe that having an idol is often VERY GOOD to the point where you take his/her positive traits and copy them (like persistence, etc). But copying a person to a point where you are the SECOND RATE of him/her is plain stupid.For example, I like Winston Churchill. I like his persistence and quotes about success. But there’s some things I don’t like about him too. I take only his positive traits and see to model them at me. I leave out the negative ones. Simple as that.
我相信有了偶像，就有利于人们接受并模仿他们的优秀品质（比如坚毅等等）。但是如果完全复制别人，成为了他/她的“二流版本”，就愚不可及了。举个例子，我喜欢温斯顿·丘吉尔。我欣赏他的坚持不懈与他对成功的见解。但是他的有些方面我并不苟同。我取其精华，并作为自己的榜样。同时去其糟粕，摒弃消极的品质。各位读者们可以以此为例。</p>

<!-- more -->

<p><a href="http://everet.org/wp-content/uploads/2012/01/22_101101194832_1.jpg"><img src="http://everet.org/wp-content/uploads/2012/01/22_101101194832_1.jpg" alt="" /></a></p>

<h4 id="action-is-the-real-measure-of-intelligence--napoleon-hill">2.Action is the real measure of intelligence.- Napoleon Hill</h4>

<h4 id="napoleon-hill">行动才是智慧真正的度量衡——拿破仑·希尔（Napoleon Hill，世界上最伟大的励志成功大师之一）</h4>

<p>Actually, this quote was also told by Andrew Carnegie, the richest man on Earth 100 years ago. I see so many people going to schools, universities. I see my teachers say that I need to study hard, memorize root lessons to become “somebody”. Then I remind myself of Bill Gates who dropped out. I remind myself of Steve Jobs who also dropped out. Thousands upon thousands of successful people who dropped out of high school and universities. They did not choose root memorization as their education. They choose action, failures and successes as their primary action. That was their intelligence. And they got very rich by it.
事实上，这句话百年前的世界第一富翁安德鲁·卡内基（Andrew Carnegie）②就说过了。我看到太多的人进入高等学府，听到我的老师说我必须努力学习，记住些基本课文，将来成为“某些人”。然后我不禁想到了辍学的比尔·盖茨，辍学的史蒂芬·乔布斯。成千上百名成功人士都放弃了高中和大学的学业。他们并没有选择把基础知识的记忆作为培养自己的方式，而选择了行动 ——让成功和失败成为他们主要的行动。这就是他们的智慧，并且以此得到了巨大财富。</p>

<h4 id="each-morning-when-i-open-my-eyes-i-say-to-myself-i-not-events-have-the-power-to-make-me-happy-or-unhappy-today-i-can-choose-which-it-shall-be-yesterday-is-dead-tomorrow-hasnt-arrived-yet-i-have-just-one-day-today-and-im-going-to-be-happy-in-it---groucho-marx">3.Each morning when I open my eyes I say to myself: I, not events, have the power to make me happy or unhappy today. I can choose which it shall be. Yesterday is dead, tomorrow hasn’t arrived yet. I have just one day, today, and I’m going to be happy in it. - Groucho Marx</h4>

<h4 id="groucho-marx">每天清晨，当我睁开眼睛，我告诉自己：我今天快乐或是不快乐，并非由我所遭遇的事情造成的，而应该取决于我自己。我可以自己选择事情的发展方向。昨日已逝，明朝未及，我只有过好每一个今天，唯一的今天。——格劳乔·马克斯（Groucho Marx，上世纪好莱坞著名喜剧演员）</h4>

<p>Yesterday’s tomorrow is today. Tomorrow’s yesterday is today. Why care about the past (don’t get me wrong, you can learn a lot from analyzing the past). But I see people that go into over-analyzing the past and do too much planning for the future. What about the…PRESENT. What about enjoying the present moment? Have you ever thought about that? If not, it’s time to reconsider.
昨日的明天是今天。明天的昨日是今天。为什么要计较于过去呢（先别急着纠正我的错误，你确实可以在评判过去中学到许多）。但是我发现有的人过分地瞻前顾后了。为何不想想“现在”呢？为何不及时行乐呢？如果你的回答是“不”，那么是时候该重新考虑一下了。</p>

<h4 id="the-greatest-barrier-to-success-is-the-fear-of-failure---sven-goran-eriksson">4.The greatest barrier to success is the fear of failure - Sven Goran Eriksson</h4>

<h4 id="sven-goran-eriksson">  成功的最大障碍是惧怕失败——斯文·戈兰·埃里克森（Sven Goran Eriksson）</h4>

<p>“Try And Fail, but don’t Fail to Try” - Stephen Kaggwa
“尝试后才放弃，但是不要放弃尝试。”——史蒂芬·卡格瓦（Stephen Kaggwa）</p>

<p>“I didn’t fail the test, I just found 1000 ways to do it wrong” - Benjamin Franklin
“我并未在试验中失败，我只是寻找了1000中错误的做法。”——本杰明·富兰克林</p>

<p>The lesson: don’t be afraid to fail. If you do, try again. Take babies for example. What a baby is learning to walk and fails he doesn’t sit down and say: “Damn it, I’m such a failure, I quit”. Not a SINGLE BABY does that. Instead, he tries again and again and again. If one approach does not work, try another and another and another.</p>

<p>这些句子都教育我们：不要惧怕失败。如果你失败了，重新尝试。以婴儿为例，当一个婴孩学步摔倒后，他不会坐下来说：“靠，我真失败，我放弃。”并且不是一个婴儿会如此做，他们都会反反复复，一次一次地尝试。如果一条路走不通，那就走走其他途径，不断尝试。</p>

<p>Fear of failure is simply a trait imposed by society. Nobody is born with the fear of failure. Remember that.
惧怕失败仅仅是社会导致的一种品质，没有人生来害怕失败，记住这一点。</p>

<h4 id="better-to-do-something-imperfectly-than-to-do-nothing-flawlessly---robert-schuller">5.Better to do something imperfectly than to do nothing flawlessly - Robert Schuller</h4>

<h4 id="robert-schuller">  宁愿做事而犯错，也不要为了不犯错而什么都不做——罗伯特·舒勒（Robert schuller）</h4>

<p>Do not wait for a perfect time to start doing something. It may be hard at the beginning and you’ll get used as time passes by. There will be no perfect time always, so do things even when it doesn’t feel it is the right time to do so.
不一定要等到时机完全成熟才动手。开头也许艰难，但是随着时间的流逝，你会渐渐熟悉你的事业。世上往往没有完美的时机，所以当你觉得做某事还不是时候，先做起来再说吧。</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
